const name = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is the correct syntax for referring the external style sheet?",
    optionOne: "<style src = example.css>",
    optionTwo: "<style src='example.css'>",
    optionThree: "<stylesheet> example.css </stylesheet>",
    optionFour: "<link rel='stylesheet' type='text/css' href='example.css'>",
    answer: "<link rel='stylesheet' type='text/css' href='example.css'>",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is",
    optionOne: "bgcolor",
    optionTwo: "color",
    optionThree: "background-color",
    optionFour: "All of the above",
    answer: "background-color",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What type of CSS is generally recommended for designing large web pages?",
    optionOne: "inline",
    optionTwo: "internal",
    optionThree: "external",
    optionFour: "none of the above",
    answer: "external",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following CSS selector is used to specify a rule to bind a particular unique element?",
    optionOne: "tag",
    optionTwo: "id",
    optionThree: "class",
    optionFour: " both class and tag",
    answer: "id",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following type of HTML tag is used to define an internal style sheet?",
    optionOne: "<script>",
    optionTwo: "<link>",
    optionThree: "<class>",
    optionFour: "<style>",
    answer: "<style>",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following are the CSS Extension Prefixes for Webkit?",
    optionOne: "-chrome",
    optionTwo: "-web",
    optionThree: "-o-",
    optionFour: "-webkit",
    answer: "-webkit",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following are the CSS Extension Prefixes for Webkit?",
    optionOne: "-chrome",
    optionTwo: "-web",
    optionThree: "-o-",
    optionFour: "-webkit",
    answer: "-webkit",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is the first CSS specification to become an official W3C Recommendation?",
    optionOne: "CSS level 2",
    optionTwo: "(X)HTML CSS",
    optionThree: "CSS level 1",
    optionFour: "-webkit",
    answer: "CSS level 1",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following function defines a linear gradient as a CSS image?",
    optionOne: "gradient()",
    optionTwo: "linear-gradient()",
    optionThree: "grayscale()",
    optionFour: "image()",
    answer: "linear-gradient()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following CSS property defines the different properties of all four sides of an elementâ€™s border in a single declaration?",
    optionOne: "border-collapse",
    optionTwo: "border-width",
    optionThree: "padding",
    optionFour: "border",
    answer: "border-width",
  },
];
